{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Wheelchair Ramp Repair Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/43283/":{"taskOID":43283,"originalTaskOID":43283,"setID":771,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4442,"questionDisplayText":"Ramp material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the ramp made of? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3803,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Metal","answerDisplayText":"Metal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1553,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7084,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood rails","answerDisplayText":"Wood rails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7138,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wrought iron rails","answerDisplayText":"Wrought iron rails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3828,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Metal tube rails","answerDisplayText":"Metal tube rails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4444,"questionDisplayText":"Repair Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be repaired? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5027,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ramp","answerDisplayText":"Ramp","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7109,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wooden handrails/pickets","answerDisplayText":"Wooden handrails/pickets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Metal handrails/pickets","answerDisplayText":"Metal handrails/pickets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":669,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Add/replace handrails","answerDisplayText":"Add/replace handrails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":639,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Add non-skid surface","answerDisplayText":"Add non-skid surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1346,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Change slope","answerDisplayText":"Change slope","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1341,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Change length or direction","answerDisplayText":"Change length or direction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4445,"questionDisplayText":"Ramp Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the ramp? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2658,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Front door","answerDisplayText":"Front door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":921,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Back door","answerDisplayText":"Back door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5670,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Side door","answerDisplayText":"Side door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3211,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Indoors","answerDisplayText":"Indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4446,"questionDisplayText":"Ramp Use","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How is the ramp used?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7037,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"With walker","answerDisplayText":"With walker","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7035,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"With motorized scooter","answerDisplayText":"With motorized scooter","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7036,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"With motorized wheelchair","answerDisplayText":"With motorized wheelchair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7034,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"With manual wheelchair","answerDisplayText":"With manual wheelchair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4442,"questionDisplayText":"Ramp material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the ramp made of? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3803,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Metal","answerDisplayText":"Metal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1553,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7084,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood rails","answerDisplayText":"Wood rails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7138,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wrought iron rails","answerDisplayText":"Wrought iron rails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3828,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Metal tube rails","answerDisplayText":"Metal tube rails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3803,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Metal","answerDisplayText":"Metal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1553,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7084,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood rails","answerDisplayText":"Wood rails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7138,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wrought iron rails","answerDisplayText":"Wrought iron rails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3828,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Metal tube rails","answerDisplayText":"Metal tube rails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4444,"questionDisplayText":"Repair Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be repaired? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5027,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ramp","answerDisplayText":"Ramp","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7109,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wooden handrails/pickets","answerDisplayText":"Wooden handrails/pickets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Metal handrails/pickets","answerDisplayText":"Metal handrails/pickets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":669,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Add/replace handrails","answerDisplayText":"Add/replace handrails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":639,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Add non-skid surface","answerDisplayText":"Add non-skid surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1346,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Change slope","answerDisplayText":"Change slope","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1341,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Change length or direction","answerDisplayText":"Change length or direction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5027,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ramp","answerDisplayText":"Ramp","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7109,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wooden handrails/pickets","answerDisplayText":"Wooden handrails/pickets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Metal handrails/pickets","answerDisplayText":"Metal handrails/pickets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":669,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Add/replace handrails","answerDisplayText":"Add/replace handrails","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":639,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Add non-skid surface","answerDisplayText":"Add non-skid surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1346,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Change slope","answerDisplayText":"Change slope","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1341,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Change length or direction","answerDisplayText":"Change length or direction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4445,"questionDisplayText":"Ramp Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the ramp? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2658,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Front door","answerDisplayText":"Front door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":921,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Back door","answerDisplayText":"Back door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5670,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Side door","answerDisplayText":"Side door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3211,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Indoors","answerDisplayText":"Indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2658,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Front door","answerDisplayText":"Front door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":921,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Back door","answerDisplayText":"Back door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5670,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Side door","answerDisplayText":"Side door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3211,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Indoors","answerDisplayText":"Indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4446,"questionDisplayText":"Ramp Use","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How is the ramp used?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7037,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"With walker","answerDisplayText":"With walker","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7035,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"With motorized scooter","answerDisplayText":"With motorized scooter","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7036,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"With motorized wheelchair","answerDisplayText":"With motorized wheelchair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7034,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"With manual wheelchair","answerDisplayText":"With manual wheelchair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7037,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"With walker","answerDisplayText":"With walker","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7035,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"With motorized scooter","answerDisplayText":"With motorized scooter","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7036,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"With motorized wheelchair","answerDisplayText":"With motorized wheelchair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7034,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"With manual wheelchair","answerDisplayText":"With manual wheelchair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/43283/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":43283,"taskName":"Disability Ramps - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Wheelchair Ramps","xmTaskDescriptor":"Wheelchair Ramp Repair Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1713,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Disability Ramps modify access","textMessagingName":"Repr Disab Ramp","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes simulated wood \u0026 wood substitutes. For concrete ramps, see installing concrete flatwork. These experts know the recommended widths, slopes \u0026 understand how to handle rails \u0026 landings to maximize safety.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes simulated wood \u0026 wood substitutes.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Wooden Wheelchair Ramps.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Repair a Wheelchair Ramp \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Repair an Access Ramp","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":20,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Disability Ramp Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Disability Ramps - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Disability Ramp Project","urlName":"Disability-Ramps-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Wheelchair Ramp Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Reviews","searchKeywords":"Disability,Ramps,modify,access","emcCategoryOid":-12021,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":771,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}